appurse.com 2019-07-24

# Cookies & Privacy Policy

According to GDPR and EU user content policy, we update our cookies policy and privacy policy to explain what information we collect, how we use it and how to manage your cookies settings.

**What Are Cookies and Why Do We Use Them?**

Cookies are small-sized text files saved by your browser on your device (computer, mobile phone, tablet, etc) and the browser will send this file to our server only when you visit our website. 

Cookies are used to collect non-personal information like your device, operating system, browser type, and how you have interacted with our websites. We use cookies technology to improve the quality of our website and provide personalized advertising tailored to your interests. By default, your browser is set to allow cookies, but you can always choose to block cookies in your browser's settings.

**What Kind of Cookies Do We Use?**

● Necessary Cookies

Necessary Cookies are required to deliver the services you request in our website. These Cookies play an essential role in operating this site and displaying it properly. These necessary Cookies cannot be disabled.No information about your browsing habits is gathered by Necessary cookies. 

● Analytics Cookies

We use Google Analytics Cookies to analyze and measure our audience, traffic, and engagement with the site. Cookies are automatically enabled on our site upon your visit and you can opt out of these Analytics Cookies at any time by following the instructions set out below. For more information on how Google uses cookies, please check [here. ](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites)

● Interest-Based Advertising 

Interest-Based Advertising Cookies are used to analyze your interests and preferences, showing you personalized ads on this site or elsewhere, and measuring the effectiveness of advertising. These Interest-Based Advertising Cookies may be deployed by us, advertisers, ad-tech providers, and others. You can withdraw your consent to Interest-Based Advertising Cookies by following the instructions below. 

Please understand that if you withdraw your consent to Interest-Based Advertising Cookies, certain features may not function correctly. You will see non-personalized instead of ads based on your interests.

● Third Party Cookies

Some of the cookies on the website are operated by third parties. Some of our third-party links are designed to automatically transmit users’ information onto the third party’s landing page when you choose to “click” upon a third party’s advertisement or promotion. We have no control over these third parties or their use of cookies. Please check the websites of these third parties for detailed information on how they use cookies. Besides cookies, technologies like pixel tags, web beacons, eTags may also be used to improve our understanding of things like site traffic, visitor behavior and promotional campaigns. 

Below is a list of all the parties that may use cookies or your personal data:

Cookie | Type | Description  
---|---|---  
Google Analytics, Google AdSense, DoubleClick | Site analytics (Google Analytics) | Google operates the Google Display Network: a collection of millions of websites and mobile applications that are powered by display advertising, including many Google services like YouTube. Google also operates the DoubleClick digital advertising platform: the ad technology foundation to create, transact, and manage digital advertising for the world’s buyers, creators, and sellers. The DoubleClick platform includes the DoubleClick Advertising Exchange and Double Click Bid Manager. To learn more about how Google collect and use information for online advertising, please visit [Google Privacy & Terms](https://policies.google.com/privacy)  
Pinterest | Social media | Pinterest lets you organize and share all the things you find on the internet. People use pinboards to plan record their ourfits, decorate their homes, find interesting items and more. [Pinterest Privacy Policy](http://pinterest.com/about/privacy/)  
  
**How to Opt out of Cookies?**

We provide several opt-out solutions if you want to withdraw your consent. Please understand that certain features on our websites may not work correctly if you disable all cookies. Please also note that after applying these settings, you will still see advertising, although it may not be tailored to your interests using information collected from cookies and similar technologies.

If you don't want us to use cookies when you visit this site, click [here](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/clear-cookies-installed.html) for information on how to change your browser settings to reject cookies. Disabling these cookies won’t turn off advertising on our websites, and you will see non-personalized ads instead of targeted ads.

● Google Analytics Cookies Opt-out 

Google provides some tools to control its cookies: If you want to turn off Google Analytics cookies, this [ opt-out browser add-on ](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) can be helpful.

Google Safety Centre also provides a tool enabling you to control the data used for serving ads to you. You can see it [here.](https://www.google.com/safetycenter/tools/#!/)

● Other Cookies Controls

If you wish to block other cookies, you can use the browser-level cookie controls. Most browsers allow you to manage your cookie settings which can usually be found in the "Settings", "Options" or "Preferences" menu of your browser.

Manage cookie settings in [Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?co=GENIE.Platform%3DDesktop) and [Chrome Android](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?co=GENIE.Platform%3DAndroid) and [Chrome iOS](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?co=GENIE.Platform%3DiOS)

Manage cookie settings in [Firefox](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences)

Manage cookie settings in [Internet Explorer](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies)

Manage cookie settings in [Microsoft Edge](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/4468242/microsoft-edge-browsing-data-and-privacy-microsoft-privacy)

Manage cookie settings in [Safari iOS](https://support.apple.com/en-gb/HT201265)

**Privacy Policy**

Our website collects and manages user data according to the following Privacy Policy. By using the Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

● The Information We Collect

In some cases, we collect information regarding what pages within site you look at, how long you look at them for and how many times you look at them. This information allows us to optimize our website and make sure that we provide the best possible experience for our users.

● How We Use the Information

We may use this information to learn how this website is being used and to gauge the popularity of different parts of the site. Knowing how many times specific sections of the site are viewed, we can adjust our contents and make improvements to optimize our service. 

● Track abuse if it occurs.

We will disclose information we have when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order. We may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request.

● Property Claim

The trademarks and logos of all the merchants displayed on the website are the property of their respective owners. Our website is not affiliated or associated with any of them. 

● Safety Concern

Please be assured that this site only provides original apps and apk files without any cheat, modifications or virus. Your personal information will NOT be shared with any other third party without your explicit permission.

● Policy Change

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Services after such changes have been first posted.

#### Contact US

Our email dress is contact@appurse.com. If you have any question or suggestion about the website, please feel free to contact us.
